You know what financial health is
It is a set of indicators on How to manage your financial life
How much your daily behaviors help you to be prepared for an economic shock
And what is your financial capacity to achieve your personal goals and in general Live your life
According to the financial health network in the United States, financial health is made up of four pillars
Spending
Savings where investment is also talked about
Planning and debt
At this time we will focus on the pillar of now
Let's see what the cell phone consists of
eleven
Point number one
You have good saving habits that allow you to be prepared to face its expiration
Point number two
You are saving for the short term, that is, you have enough liquid savings, reports emergency
Point number 3
You have enough long-term savings or assets
At this time you do not meet the 23 points of this Pillar do not worry
That's what we're here for
I assure you that it will not be a tedious path, we work a lot on this platform to make it simple and fun for you now.